Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/evy-quyen (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

SQL Server Management Studio
Agile Methodologies
Smoke Testing

Certifications

ETS Test | Listening and Reading - Score 795

Certified Tester Foundation Level (CTFL)

Nguyen Phuong Quyen

Test Engineering | ISTQB Foundation Certificate
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

I have been doing QA Manual Engineering for the more than one year and I've being worked for a company based Sweden recently. I have developed a specialization in aiding companies and teams to ensure the utmost quality of their product prior to release. I've been able to help my clients to really release their product with as perfect as possible in less than six months.

Experience

TLab West AB
Software Tester
March 2024 - Present (1 year 2 months)

KMS Technology, Inc.
Test Engineer
April 2022 - July 2023 (1 year 4 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Project: Kaypay - the Fintech application that providing convenient shopping for users by BNPL method

Education

APTECH Computer Education

Advance Diploma, Computer Software Engineering · (August 2019 - December 2021)